This minister attacked me!
This is not part
of our agreement!
What are you talking about?
Don't fucking touch me!
No! Don't! Don't!
Orya!
Hey!
- You need to watch this.
- You watch it.
- I can't sit through that again.
- Jake.
We must be methodical
and miss nothing.
Come on.
- Who gave you this tape?
- I don't know.
Keep it on, or it will swell.
It was just dropped at my door.
This minister attacked me!
That fucker.
That's one of the two Tozawa thugs who
attacked me in my house yesterday.
The man with your friend.
Do you realize who that is?
Jotaro Shigematsu...
Vice Minister of Foreign Affairs.
Holy shit.
At the door?
Shimoda-san!
Why isn't the new wiring here?
The store apologized
because the delivery was delayed.
I'll go by the store.
Busy, busy.
Can I help you?
First day in business with you.
Just checking in.
I was told Sato would be
my point person.
Well, you got me today.
Knock yourself out.
Sato, where are you,
and why is Kobayashi in my club?
- What are you doing?
- It's my turn.
Someone looking for Sato.
Who the fuck are you?
Kaito. Sato is my brother.
Sato ever mention a brother?
- Never.
- Our father is in the hospital.
He doesn't have much longer.
He is asking for my brother.
He isn't answering his phone.
Any of you heard from Sato yet?
No.
When we see him, we'll tell him
you came by. Now get the fuck out.
Thank you.
Sorry.
You know what to do.
Take this straight to my editor,
get it published as soon as possible.
I will reach out to my contacts.
But Tozawa is very good
at making people disappear.
Maybe you should lay low.
At least till the story runs.
You just said that he threatened
Junko and the kids.
I won't look
into him specifically.
Whoever sent you that
also touched this.
I'll try and lift a print and see
if I can find out who sent it.
Beyond that, this will be
impossible to ignore.
And then...
I will arrest Tozawa personally.
You make it public.
I'll take it from there.
I still can't help but feel
if I hadn't have screwed up
that airport raid that Tozawa
would already be arrested,
and Polina would've never gotten
on that boat.
Jake.
You are not responsible
for another man's misdeeds.
And you are not the only
one who's made mistakes.
Now go.
Hello?
Yes.
What?
- I'm looking for my brother.
- What is your brother's name?
- Akiro Sato.
- He is in Room 916.
Thank you.
How did you find me?
Your phone number was in his wallet.
My brother... can you save him?
We're monitoring him closely.
Sato! Where the fuck is he?
Come here!
- What are you doing? Stop!
- Come here.
- Sato!
- Please be quiet!
Daikou!
- You're bothering others!
- Daikou!
- Hey! It's that kid!
- That's the room!
Doctor, it's my brother's...
Hayaku!
Who are you? You can't be in here!
He looks like shit.
Get him up.
What are you doing?
- Take all that shit off him.
- Wait... Absolutely not!
- Do it, or I'll break your face.
- You can't take my brother!
He's our brother.
If you move him he could die!
The police were just here.
They will be back soon!
- Who do you think called us?
- What?
Cops don't care about us.
A Chihara-kai mess gets
cleaned up by Chihara-kai.
Don't worry, Sato.
We'll get those fuckers.
Vice Minister Shigematsu.
On tape with a murdered prostitute.
She wasn't a prostitute.
We cannot call it a murder.
Does anyone think
that girl is still alive?
Baku...
We have no body. And even with a body,
it's manslaughter at best.
He ID'd the girl,
confirmed she's missing...
And we have what's on this tape.
We run with that.
This is the biggest government
scandal in years.
This doesn't leave the building.
Have copies made.
I'll pull the stills. Find a good shot
of Shigematsu we can run.
You, write the article.
Jake brought in the tape.
He should get the story.
Dead girls failed by the system...
Is your area.
Besides, weren't you warned
to stay away from this?
- Yes, sir.
- You two will work on it, together.
Yes, sir.
We'll need a comment
from the Vice Minister.
We'll never get in to see him
on such short notice.
We hold the story
until we get the comment.
I have contacts at the Ministry
I'll make some calls.
Let's get to it!
You have one new message.
Hey, me again. I haven't heard
from you since yesterday.
I talked to Polina's roommate,
still nothing.
Seriously, Jake, if you have any news
on Polina, call me, please.
- You want coffee?
- I'm good, thanks.
Everyone is talking
about the girl on the tape.
- You knew her, right?
- I told you not to ask about that.
It's fine. I knew her, yeah.
If there's anything we can do,
let us know.
Yes.
The boat she died on, the Yoshino,
can you check the registry?
Okay.
- If Tozawa's name is on it...
- Then he goes in the article.
Ozaki got us an appointment
with the Vice Minister
Shigematsu in the morning.
- We can't wait that long.
- We don't have a choice.
Go home and get some rest.
You two, come with me.
Yoshino.
We're on it.
How is he?
His organs are unaffected.
But there's a serious
chance of infection.
The next few days are critical.
Who'll stay with him?
I will.
No. I will stay with him.
Go. Let him rest.
Thank you, Oyabun.
Sato.
Whoever did this...
They will suffer.
I apologize that my schedule did not
permit me to see you yesterday.
Of course. We understand.
How can I help my friends
at the Meicho?
Ozaki-san was vague
about the focus of your piece.
Does the name Yoshino
mean anything to you?
Should it?
We have questions, Vice Minister
Shigematsu, about you and this woman.
That isn't me.
We have footage of you watching this girl
be beaten until she appears dead.
The story runs tomorrow.
This is your opportunity to comment.
My comment is, "no comment."
You're not the one who killed the girl.
You're being set up by Shinzo Tozawa...
Who made this tape to blackmail you.
Isn't that right?
Give us Tozawa and we'll make
that clear in the article.
Is this who the Meicho employs now?
Slovenly foreigners with no decorum?
I apologize for my colleague.
I'll have a word with him.
Thank you.
Let's go.
I wasn't bribing him.
I was trying to back-foot him
so that he would give us Tozawa.
Jake! You asked a government
official for information
in exchange
for going easy on him!
- It was a calculated risk!
- Like with the loan officer, Sugita?
How well did that go?
Do you want another suicide
on your hands?
Well, that's a low blow.
Maruyama-san. If we can connect
Polina's murder to Tozawa,
why shouldn't we press
that angle?
Because we don't have Tozawa.
We have the vice minister,
one nameless yakuza,
and another missing woman
presumed dead,
who deserves
to have her story told.
Katagiri-san.
This was just left for you.
By who?
At the reception.
DETECTIVE KATAGIRI
MIYAMOTO, ROOM 107.
I wanted you to have that back.
I didn't call earlier because
I didn't want it to be true.
I'm so sorry.
Did they find her body?
No, not yet.
They're still looking.
I promise you, Sam.
People will know what they did to her.
Do you wanna... get a cup
of coffee or something?
I wanna be alone.
I was actually hoping that you could tell
me a little bit about her.
- What do you mean?
- Polina.
Like where she's from,
what brought her here.
I wanna do right by her.
In the article.
She deserves that.
You came here
to interview me for a story.
No, no. I just...
I don't want people to see her
as another faceless victim.
The people should know the funny,
the kind person that she was.
You couldn't wait a day
before coming to me with this?
Whatever story is gonna run,
it's coming out tomorrow.
- So, this is our only chance to...
- Get out of my fucking club.
Trendy Haiyu.
What did you learn?
Listen. The boat is not registered under
any known associates of Tozawa.
- So, it took a while. But I got the name.
- Who is it?
Someone named Misaki Taniguchi.
Okay. Uh, thanks.
I'll look into it.
Bye.
- Misaki.
- Jake. You cannot be here.
I made sure nobody saw me.
I made sure of it.
I need to talk
to you about something.
- What happened to you?
- Oh, it's nothing.
Occupational hazard.
Did he do this because of me?
What do you know
about the Yoshino?
- I don't know what that is.
- It's Tozawa's boat.
Girls go on it,
entertaining men for money.
A woman I know just went,
and she was killed.
Jake. I am so sorry.
Misaki, you're listed
as the owner of this boat.
That's impossible.
- Well, your signature's on the registry.
- Then someone forged it.
I don't know
anything about this.
He shares nothing
with me.
I'm gonna have
to write about this.
It's your name.
You're connected to Tozawa,
which connects him to the boat.
If you publish my name,
any future I might have had
beyond Tozawa
will be impossible.
So, is there any other info
you can get from him?
Anything other than you
that connects him to the boat?
He isn't here.
He left his hotel two nights ago.
He flew off somewhere.
Where?
When is he coming back?
I don't know. I told you,
he tells me nothing.
Jake.
You must leave me out of it.
Please.
A source gave me a tip.
Soon as I found him, I called it in.
He was a good cop. Well-liked.
Still...
But he did enjoy taking risks.
Then again, I wouldn't expect him
to be shooting meth.
He had a thing about needles.
Makes you wonder...
What do you mean?
Maybe this wasn't an accident.
I know you two were going after Tozawa.
If Tozawa thought you two were getting
close to something...
I wouldn't put it past him.
Would you?
Be careful, Katagiri.
Kaoru...
From today you will take
over the resort.
Take over?
Mother!
That's right, starting today you will
begin your training.
Cool!
Mother, please don't make
jokes like that.
I'm serious.
Serious? She just got here!
Hey, it's me again.
Where are you?
I really need
to see you tonight.
Call me.
After that,
it appears he was taken
by the Tozawa-gumi.
These were the events leading
to Miyamoto's death.
My apologies for reporting this so late.
I authorized a sting on a crooked cop.
Not an undercover operation inside
the Tozawa-gumi!
You put Miyamoto's back against a wall,
and now he's dead.
If the press finds out a cop was
working for Tozawa...
This department will never recover.
So Detective Miyamoto died tragically
of a heart attack.
You can go.
Respectfully, Assistant Commissioner.
Tozawa has murdered one of our own.
We must hit back.
Allow me to put together a task force.
Give me security for my family.
You think this office is going to trust
you with a task force after this?
The threat against your family.
Miyamoto's death. They're your fault.
Go look after your family.
Let things settle.
- That won't be necessary.
- Katagiri.
That wasn't a suggestion.
Had to be one of Tozawa's guys.
They're the only ones who would try
that shit with us.
Sato took it in the stomach, right?
So he probably saw the guy.
Sato's regained consciousness.
Doctor says he's gonna make it.
- He say who jumped him?
- Not yet.
But we'll know soon enough.
Pick me up in 30 minutes.
I've been calling and calling.
Why did you not answer the phone?
I've been worried sick.
Did you get some sleep?
You drag us out of bed
in the middle of the night...
And send us to my mother's
with no explanation.
- What do you think?
- I'm sorry.
Will you tell me what's happening?
I told you.
Someone called in a threat.
It happens all the time
but we have to follow up.
You should be home soon.
Your daughters need you.
Tell them I miss them.
Be safe.
Then you can tell them yourself.
THE BOAT SEEMS TO BE A CRUISER.
IT IS REGISTERED UNDER...
...THE NAME OF A YAKUZA BOSS'S
SUPPOSED MISTRESS...
...FORMER MODEL...
...MISAKI TANIGUCHI.
What do you want?
It's not what I want.
It's what I can give you.
Give us?
Please leave your name
and number after the beep.
Akiko-san, it's Samantha.
You're not working at Onyx tonight, right?
Give me a call. Let's go out.
Another.
Hi, it's Erika.
Leave me a message.
Hey, Mama-san Erika.
It's your former
number one girl.
I know it's been a while.
I just thought...
You free tonight?
Call me back.
Did you hear?
Jake's article connects Tozawa
to Yoshino.
The boat is registered
to his mistress.
Really? How did you find out the name
on the registry was a mistress?
It's a long story, but...
the important thing
is we're gonna nail Tozawa.
I wonder what he'll do to her
when your article comes out.
Let's talk about
something other than work.
Sure.
I have started baking.
Cakes. Pastries. Petit fours.
- You have an oven?
- Of course not. But my parents do.
I find it relieves stress.
Do you have one of the things
that squeezes filling into pastry?
They are called piping bags.
And I have several.
Oh, I'm sure you do.
Hello, Maruyama-san.
Okay!
- Jake.
- What the hell happened?
Please excuse us.
They think someone left
a cigarette burning in an ashtray.
It all went up in flames.
But they made copies
of the videotape, right?
They were all
in that safe.
Everything inside melted
from the heat.
We can still run
the article, right?
Without that tape, anything
written about him is libel.
We would be sued.
And we would lose.
No article?
What, the Vice Minister
just gets off scot-free?
You know this wasn't
an accident, right?
What, this all just happened
to be destroyed today?
Fuck!
He's here.
Good evening, Oyabun!
You seem to be lost.
If I may...
He confessed to stabbing
one of his own.
When he heard your man would live...
He came running to us for protection.
My oyabun left the country recently...
He is very ill.
He hid his illness well.
I'm not convinced he'll return.
Alive, in any case.
Some battles cannot be won.
I never agreed with Tozawa's move
on Chihara-kai territory.
This was bad business.
In his absence,
I would look to mend fences.
I hope that returning the traitor...
Will be the first step...
In ending hostilities between us.
I will be in touch. To discuss further.
That's all for now.
Your drink's right there.
Hi, it's Erika.
Leave me a message.
Erika.
It's me again.
I should have said...
I owe you an apology. I know.
I disappeared. I'm sorry.
Can I see you tonight?
I just need to see
somebody tonight who knows me.
Your drink's right there.
- Call me back.
- Just come inside for a drink.
Sorry, another time.
Beautiful girl,
good evening.
Just come inside for a drink.
Get the fuck off me!
Fuck you!
Fuck this place!
Hey! Do not go
in that host club.
Those guys are evil.
They'll take your money!
They'll all take your money!
They'll ruin your life!
Get the fuck off me!
No tape, no story.
No accident.
Tozawa is... an octopus.
Tentacles extending everywhere.
Cut off one...
another grows in its place.
But... you know what happened.
You can look into it.
I cannot.
Are you serious?
I've been told officially...
that the investigation
ends here.
But why?
Detective Miyamoto
was found dead today.
What I'm going to tell you
you will never write. Never repeat.
We were building a case together
against Tozawa in secret.
The octopus found out.
Miyamoto's death was made
to look like an overdose,
but Tozawa is responsible.
That son of a bitch!
That sick.
Jake. Listen to me.
You are going to do nothing.
My life, my family's life, your life.
Are all in danger.
He is watching us.
Your friend Polina. Miyamoto.
They will have their justice.
Trust me.
Our day to get Tozawa will come.
But for now... we wait.
And do what?
You did not come to Tokyo
in pursuit of one man.
There are other stories.
Other crimes to be exposed.
That is your job. Is it not?
And so he returns.
Can you move your hand?
- Yes...
- Good.
Bring him.
It is just that you do it.
Give me the knife.
Why hesitate?
This dog betrayed you.
Me. This organization.
He must not live.
No... more...
Your life belongs to him now.
You will dedicate yourself to proving
worthy of his mercy.
Yes, sir.
Thank you, Oyabun...
So painful.
Hey, you okay?
No.
Where is the information from?
Yes. I will look into this.
It's not your shift.
No, I'd rather be here
and do some work.
Jake-san...
did you hear Miyamoto
was found dead today?
Yeah, I just heard.
The police are saying
it was a heart attack.
But a source of mine
just told me
he hears there's much more
to his death.
- Like what?
- I'm going to find out.
He did have
serious heart issues.
He told me a few times
that he had ventricular arrhythmia.
Yeah, it was a thing my dad
always said was a real killer.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Miyamoto was
pretty shaken up about it.
He said he needed
to change his life.
I see.
Sorry, man.
Would've made a great story.
Thank you.
Samantha!
Come on!
Don't be slowpoke!
- My God...
- You got this!
You got this.
You are a terrible person.
So, I am... ten, 11.
The age you get animal
as responsibility.
But mine was a sheep.
I named her Bela,
which means "white."
- That's very cute.
- Thank you.
So one night, my grandfather
ties Bela to a tree.
And he gives me long gun.
And he sits me
maybe 20 meters away.
- Oh, no. He made you shoot...
- No, listen.
So, my grandfather says,
"Stay up all night. If bear
or wolf comes, you protect her."
- And he goes back inside bed.
- What'd you do?
Girl, what do you think?
I stay awake.
But then...
Three o'clock in the morning, wolf.
Bang. I shoot. I miss.
And wolf jump at my Bela.
- Fuck!
- But then, bang.
Another gun behind me,
and wolf is dead.
I look.
And there's my grandfather.
All night in secret,
20 meters behind me.
And he says:
"Polina, don't ever miss."
And then he beat
the shit out of me.
- That is awful.
- No. Best lesson I ever got.
I'll never forget.
But same for you.
You see wolf,
you better not miss shot.
- Seriously, don't ever fucking miss.
- I won't. I promise.
- I will never fucking miss.
- Good.
- You think you'll ever go back?
- No. Never. You?
There's nothing to go back to.
What about your family?
I don't have a family.
Yes, you do. You have me.
You have a lovely home.
Who are you?
How did you get past security?
I know you're the one who stopped
the Yoshino story from running.
Tozawa must have been taping
you on that boat for a reason.
Keep quiet.
What did he want from you?
The next lie out of your mouth,
I take a finger.
What did he want?
He was banned from entering
the United States.
He wanted my help getting him
off the no-fly list.
I couldn't help him.
What does he want in the States?
What's so important he would try
to blackmail you?
I don't know.
I would tell you, I swear!
This meeting never happened.
If you ever say otherwise,
I'll come back.
And kill you.